[
    {
    "title": "NYU Paris",
    
    "questions": [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is the campus ID of MANOJ DHAKAL?",
        "correct_answer": "N12379849"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "When does the Spring 2024 term start?",
        "correct_answer": "January 17, 2024"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "When does the Spring 2024 term end?",
        "correct_answer": "May 14, 2024"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is the address of NYU Paris?",
        "correct_answer": "5 7 Boulevard Saint Germain, Paris, France 75005"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is the phone number for NYU Paris?",
        "correct_answer": "011-33-1-5373-2800"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Who is the Director of Outbound Immigration and Mobility?",
        "correct_answer": "Robert J. Sanford, Jr."
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What is the email address of Robert J. Sanford, Jr.?",
        "correct_answer": "robert.sanford@nyu.edu"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What is the phone number for NYU Office of Global Services?",
        "correct_answer": "(212) 998-4242"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What is the address of R\u00e9sidence Les Estudines?",
        "correct_answer": "47, avenue du G\u00e9n\u00e9ral de Gaulle, 93170 BAGNOLET"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What is the address of Maison de l'\u00cele-de-France?",
        "correct_answer": "9D boulevard Jourdan, 75014 Paris"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "What is the address of Fondation des Etats-Unis?",
        "correct_answer": "15 boulevard Jourdan, 75014 Paris"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "What is the phone number for Fondation des Etats-Unis?",
        "correct_answer": "00-33-1-53-80-68-80"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Who is the Senior Director of Student Services and Support?",
        "correct_answer": "Christopher L Nicolussi"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "What must all students provide before departure?",
        "correct_answer": "Proof of health insurance"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "In what language are courses at NYU Paris taught?",
        "correct_answer": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "What additional course must all students enroll in at NYU Paris?",
        "correct_answer": "French Language courses"
    }
    ]
    }
]